Allen Lai

Web Developer

Taipei

luckstar77y@gmail.com - +886988966591

Hello! I have 8+ years of engineer experience.

I Excellent in NodeJS, VueJS, MongoDB, C/C++, Android NDK, HTML, JS, CSS, PHP, MYSQL, ReactJS.

In the interactive video projection system, AR, image recognition and web development has been experience and produced a lot of exhibition and cases.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

WORK EXPERIENCE

NodeJS developer

BROCAS CO., LTD - Taipei - 2016 to 2017

[Zero IM system production]

- -Express
- -Socket
- -Restful API
- -RabbitMQ

[Smart Chef Club meal subscription platform production]

- -Express
- -React
- -Stripe
- -AWS SES SNS

[III Internet of Vehicles system production]

- -React
- -Echarts

[BananaFit fitness platform system production]

- -Koa
- -Vue

Software Engineer

Hiiir Inc. - Taipei - 2015 to 2016

- E commerce software research and development
- 1. Frontend official website production
- 2. Backend system production
- 3. Thirdparty community API concatenation
- 4. Mainly use Nodejs, MongoDB, HTML, JS, CSS implementation

Software Engineer

United Advertising - Taipei - 2014 to 2015

- 1. Official website production
- 2. Brand activities website production
- 3. Web game production
- 4. Backend management production
- 5. RWD production
- 6. Familiar HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3, PHP, MYSQL related technology

System Engineer

PAPAGO Inc. - Taipei - 2011 to 2013

- 1. Navigation software added, modify the function
- 2. Android phone navigation software production
- 3. Driving recorder software production
- 4.Familiar C / C ++, Android NDK

Software Engineer

ArtTech Interactive Marketing Inc. - Taipei - 2008 to 2010

- 1.Interactive Projection: Use video recognition technology to join the game, to achieve with the body can interact with the projection screen feedback, without the need to operate by the controller.
- 2.Exhibition Show: Use interactive projection technology to showcase public art and commercial advertising at large venues.
- 3.Hardware Control : Use the software to control the relevant hardware (RFID, I / O controller)
- 4. Sound Interactive : Detect sound to do feedback
- 5. Argument Reality: The camera does feedback after drawing the card
- 6.Design interactive system software
- 7.Come out to help set up hardware
- 8. Coordinate software content with customers
- 9. Discuss with the business software feasibility
- 10. Tailor the software system for customers
- 11.Familiar with C / C ++, Flash, VB

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Design in Digital Game Design

SHU-TE University - Taipei 2006 to 2010

SKILLS

Software Development (8 years), Javascript (3 years), Node.Js (3 years), Mysql (1 year), Html (3 years), Html5 (3 years), Css (3 years), Css3 (3 years), C++ (2 years), Android Development (1 year), Php (1 year), Jquery (3 years)

LINKS

https://luckstar77.github.io/

MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: Taiwan

Branch: Army Rank: Corporal 2010 to 2011

Taiwan citizen obligation

AWARDS

2008 4C Digital Design Awards

July 2009

It's Taiwan national digital design competition, I make a somatosensory interactive game to take the awads.

2007 Kaohsiung Digital Creative Design Competition

October 2007

It's Kaohsiung city digital design competition in Taiwan south, I make a monopoly game to take the awads.

2005 National High School Skills Competition of Commerce

December 2005

It's Taiwan national high school student competition, That test the logic and progamming skill, And i take the awards.

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

Level B technician for computer software application

January 2006 to Present

Skill Evaluation Center of Workforce Development Agency, Ministry of Labor

Level C technician for computer software design

October 2005 to Present

Skill Evaluation Center of Workforce Development Agency, Ministry of Labor

Visual Basic 6.0(Expert)

July 2005 to Present

Chinese Computer Education Association

Level 3 of the test of accounting ability

May 2004 to Present

Commercial Vocational Education Society

Level C technician for accounting

May 2004 to Present

Skill Evaluation Center of Workforce Development Agency, Ministry of Labor

Level B Chinese key-in 64.9 words/min

February 2004 to Present

Chinese Computer Education Association

Level C English key-in 46 words/min

February 2004 to Present

Chinese Computer Education Association

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

System

- Exposure to Node.JS environments is an asset.
- Hands on experience working with development groups to create full integrated systems.
- Experience with AWS.

Somatosensory Interactive Software

- Experience with OpenCV, C/C++
- Use video recognition technology to join the game, to achieve with the body can interact with the projection screen feedback, without the need to operate by the controller.

DevOps

- Ideally coming from an Ops heavy background.
- Excellent automation and scripting skills using CircleCI.